本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
立体脆
Cracker.
是的
Yes.
腌青瓜泡菜
Pickle dill.
很好  还有呢
Good. And?
低脂白乳酪  小盒装的  感觉发霉长毛了
Cottage cheese low fat small curd a touch of fuzz.
过期日期呢
Expiration date?
三个星期前
Three weeks ago.
绝了
Amazing.
赞啊
Yes!
搞什么呢
What's going on?
我们在玩猜零食的游戏
We're playing "guess that snack."
而你明年就可以行使选举权了
And next year you can vote.
听着  PJ  我今天碰到一个朋友
Hey listen P.J. I ran into a friend of mine today.
他正要开一个炸鸡快餐店
He's opening up a new chicken restaurant
想找个送外卖的人
And he needs a delivery guy.
老爸你不是已经有工作了吗
Dad you already have a Job.
我是在说你
I'm talking about you.
谢谢啊  可是我时间都排满了
Oh thanks but I'm already booked solid
奔波于学校和乐队之间
Between the school the band
还有我们这个零嘴比赛
our snacking competitions.
我没法把这些担子全挑起来啊
I can't do it all.
我只是一个普通人
I'm just one guy.
对  一个普通送鸡块外卖的
One guy who delivers chicken.
拿着电话号码
Here's the number.
嘿  埃米特  如果你想要我也可以给你弄份兼职
Hey Emmett if you want I might be able to get you a job too.
不用了谢谢  D先生  我已经有活干了
Oh no thanks mr. D. I already got a job.
做什么
Doing what?
我爸付我钱让我别呆在家里
My dad pays me to stay out of the house.
人家现在可是在工作呢
Working right now.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
■
校订  后期： WaitinZ
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第十一集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E11  Boys Meet Girls
嘿  小查莉  我想要给你看一件可爱绝顶的事儿
Hey charlie I want to show you something pretty adorable.
你跟妈妈正一起做瑜伽呢
You and mommy are doing yoga together.
好啦  查莉  看下一个动作
Okay Charlie. This next move
这叫做“勇士”
is called the warrior.
查莉
Charlie.
妈妈总是爱把自己放的屁推到别人头上
Mom lis to blame her farts on other people
不过我们仍然爱她
But we love her anyway.
喂  不好意思哦  老妈我才不乱放屁呢
Uh excuse me, mom doesn't fart no.
老妈只排气
She toots.
刚刚排出来的这股气还真是响亮啊
That was quite a toot you just cut.
嘿  宝贝  今天在学校怎么样
Hey, honey, how was school?
蛮好
Good.
你干嘛歪戴着帽子
Why are you wearing your hat like that?
没啥特别原因  我就喜欢这样
Oh no reason. It's how I roll.
哎呀老天  盖比你怎么了
Oh my gosh Gabe what happened?
我和查莉玩扔蛋糕来着
Charlie and I were playing pattycake
我们没留神就这样了
And things went bad.
到底谁把你欺负成这样
Who did this to you?
就是我们班的那个新生  叫什么阿乔的
This new kid in my class... Jo something.
可怜的小家伙  为啥大孩子们总是要欺负身材小的孩子呢
Poor thing. Why do the big kids always pick on the little kids?
那个冰袋不是老爸用来垫屁股的吗
Isn't that the ice pack dad puts on his butt?
恶
Eww.
哦  看来其实是你手上那个
Actually I think it's that one.
恶
Eww.
不如用冰西兰花吧  老爸不喜欢西兰花菜
What about broccoli? Dad hates broccoli.
所以他才会用那个来垫
Which is why he'd use it on his...
恶
Eww!
噢哟不会吧
Oh no.
你老爸的痔疮又犯了吗
Is dad's butt acting up again?
谁啊
Who is it?
咕唧鸡外卖
Kwikki Chikki.
每一块鸡肉都用爱心烘烤
Where every piece of chicken is grilled with love.
你好啊
Hi.
你还好吧
Hello?
呃  请拿好
Uh here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
不用找零了
Keep the change.
请愉快享用咕唧鸡
EnJoy your Kwikki Chikki.
我觉得刚才自己被爱心烘烤了
I think I was just grilled with love.
您是否介意回答几个问题呢
Would you mind answering a few questions
是为了我们的客户满意度调查
For a customer satisfaction survey?
好的
Okay.
你觉得咕唧鸡的服务
Did you find Kwikki Chikki service
是好  很好  还是非常好
To be good really good or super good?
很好
Really good.
如果一个相貌堂堂的咕唧鸡外卖员约你出去
If a good-looking Kwikki Chikki delivery dude asked you on a date
他的机会是大  很大  还是非常大呢
Would his chances be good really good or super good?
你能先把帽子摘了让我看看吗
Could you take off that cap for a second?
机会非常大
Super good.
别动
Freeze.
往后走到我这边来
Back it up and bring it here.
哦  小盖比你怎么又弄这样了
Oh, Gabe, again?
对啊  又来了
Yes again.
你这次有没有至少回击他几下啊
Well did you at least hit him back this time?
我做不到
I can't do that.
为什么不行  你应该狠狠地把这小恶霸打翻才对
Why not? You gotta take this bully down
要以牙还牙  以眼还眼
Give him a taste of his own medicine.
这是唯一能让他停止欺负人的办法
That's the only way to get him to stop.
就让我自己管自己吧
Just let me handle it.
好吧  你知道不
All right. Well you know what?
要是你不出手  大姐头我可就要亲自出手了
If you won't do it then I will.
我要好好给这孩子立点“泰迪”规则
I will school this kid Teddy-style.
嚯嚯哈嘿
Whoo!
哎呀  我的指甲要修了
Whoa I need a manicure.
PJ  埃米特打了好几次电话来
Hey P.J. Emmett's called a few times.
我迟点会打给他的啦  对了  老爸我忘了告诉你
Yeah I'll call him later. Oh dad I forgot to tell you
我那女朋友啊  哎呀我真喜欢这种称呼
My girlfriend... I love saying that...
她跟我讲了点有趣的事儿
She told me something interesting.
她怎么就已经是你的女朋友了
She's your girlfriend already?
你们不过才第一次约会而已啊
You've had one date.
那可是一次超凡脱俗的约会
One amazing date.
精彩绝伦  妙趣横生
One awesome magical fun...
她到底说了什么
What did she say?
谁啊
Who?
你女朋友啊
Your girlfriend.
哎呀  我也爱死听你这样说起她了
I love it when you say it too.
她说她妈妈和你彼此认识啊
She said her mom and you know each other.
她以前娘家名字是凯瑟琳·戴维斯
Her name used to be Katherine Davis.
凯瑟琳·戴维斯
Katherine Davis?
嗯
Um...
不太想的起来是谁啊
That's not ringing a bell.
那我还真想看看  等你想得起是谁的时候
Boy I'd sure like to see your reaction
会有什么惊人的反应
When someone does ring a bell.
那女人是谁
Who is she?
她是我跟你好上之前最后一个约会过的女生
She's the last girl I dated before you.
我在跟你旧情人的女儿约会吗
I'm dating your old girlfriend's daughter?
我希望这不会成为我以后头疼的大问题
I hope that's not gonna be a problem for me.
看起来是我要头疼才对
Seems like it might be for me.
老公  你把她的事给我交待清楚
I'd like to hear more about her bob.
哦  听着  我在和你一起之前跟很多女生玩过吗
Oh look did I date a lot of girls before you?
确实是啊
Yes sure.
我难道到处留情伤了很多人的心吗
Did I leave a trail of broken hearts?
绝对没错的
Absolutely.
但你知道吗  这一切都值得
But you know what? It was all worth it
因为我把最好的留给最后的那个人了
Because I saved the best for last.
哦
Oh.
那我也是
Me too.
我真等不及想见我那最后的一位呢
And I can't wait to meet him.
不会吧  你居然把我转到语音留言去
You did not just send me to voicemail.
对不起嘛
Sorry.
我在等我女朋友的来电呢
I'm expecting a call from my girlfriend.
你一整天都躲着我电话啊
You've been dodging my calls all day.
告诉你个好消息哈  埃米特  我们家刚装了个门铃
Hey good news Emmett. We just put in a doorbell.
那你到底找我啥事啊
What were you calling about?
看看你要不要一起玩啊
To see if you wanted to hang out.
我是很想去  可是现在我有点忙
Wish I could but I'm kind of busy right now.
好啊  亲亲女友
Hey girlfriend.
没啊  我现在一点都不忙
No I'm not doing anything right now.
当然了  我当然能去你那儿
Yeah of course I can come over.
D先生  你想一起玩吗
You want to hang out Mr. D?
我们可以玩“猜猜零嘴”的游戏哟
We could play "guess that snack."
我自己带来了遮眼布
I brought my blindfold.
你跑来干什么
What are you doing here?
给你带午饭来啦
Brought you lunch.
我的午饭自己带着呢
I already have my lunch.
那好啊  把这送给帮你做功课的
Well give this to the nerdy kid
书呆子孩子好了  真棒
who does your homework... yay!
喂  盖比
Hey, Gabe.
好啊  阿乔
Hi Jo.
你还想跑去哪里啊
Where do you think you're going?
那个就是阿乔吗
That's Jo?
我得走了
Gotta go.
你就是那个经常痛揍我弟弟的小鬼吗
You're the kid who's been pounding my brother?
可你是个小女孩啊
But you're a girl.
是又怎样  这是椅子  那是书
Yes and that's a chair. And that's a book.
我们学完了没
Are we done now?
坐下吧  阿乔  咱俩稍微谈一谈
Have a seat Jo. You and me are gonna have a little talk.
行吧
Okay.
阿乔啊  我来这里是因为我觉得很不高兴
Jo I'm here because I'm not happy.
你知道我为什么不高兴吗
And do you know why I'm not happy?
不知道  不过我很肯定你会告诉我
No but I bet you're gonna tell me.
哦是的  我不高兴是因为
Oh yes. I'm not happy
你总是欺负我的弟弟
Because you've been bullying my brother.
因为他是“好男不跟女斗”
He's a boy so he can't hit back.
但我可不是小男生
But I'm not a boy.
我才不怕你呢
You don't scare me.
当真么  那好
Really? Well
你现在害怕了吗
Do I scare you now?
才不
No.
行啊
Fair enough.
那再看看这个
How about now?
我能轻而易举折断一捆钢笔
I can do that with pens.
总之我要你别再惹我弟弟
Okay I want you to leave my brother alone
不然下次要被喀嚓的就是你自己了
Or the next thing that gets snapped will be you.
现在滚远点吧
Now get out of my face.
盖比有没有提到我呀
Does Gabe ever talk about me?
自从你揍得他变成香肠嘴以后
Ever since you gave him that fat lip
他根本没办法说一个字的
He's had trouble talking about anyone.
那他有女朋友吗
Does he have a girlfriend?
没有  你为什么要问
No and why would you...?
等下  你是不是喜欢上盖比了
Wait a minute. Do you like Gabe?
唷  真恶心
Eww that's disgusting.
好吧  一丁点
Okay maybe a little.
跟你说啊  我跟你那小朋友阿乔聊了一下哦
Oh so I had a chat with your little friend Jo.
她打你了吗
Did she punch you?
没啊
No.
踢了你
Kick you?
也没
No.
好了  反过来想想吧  她对你动心了
Okay well get this turns out she has a crush on you.
真的吗  那为何她成天要揍我啊
She does? Why does she keep hitting me?
因为她不太懂得怎么表达自己的情感
Well she has trouble expressing her feelings
所以她觉得很挫败所以用揍你来出气
And then she gets frustrated and lashes out.
所以我被打是因为我是个大帅哥吗
So I get punched for being a hunk?
可能是吧
Yep that's it.
她真的说了喜欢我吗
She really said she likes me?
哇等等  难不成你也喜欢她哦
Whoa wait do you like her too?
唷  真恶心
Eww that's just disgusting.
好吧  有一点
Okay maybe a little.
好啊  邓肯先生
Hi Mr. Duncan.
好啊  梅迪森
Hi madison.
PJ在楼下呢
P.J.'s downstairs.
谢谢
Thanks.
小包
Bobby.
凯蒂猫
Kitty-kat.
看你的样儿啊
Look at you.
也看看你的样儿啊
都来看看我好了
Look at me.
亲爱的  我想为你介绍凯蒂  凯瑟琳
Hey honey. I'd like you to meet Kitty... Katherine.
是梅迪森的妈妈
I'm Madison's mom.
你好  我是艾米  是PJ的妈妈
Hi I'm Amy. P.J.'s mom
也是鲍伯的第一个老婆
And Bob's first wife.
你能相信我们的孩子们居然在约会吗
Can you believe our kids are dating each other?
真是很深的羁绊纠葛啊  不是吗
That's a crazy twist isn't it?
喔喔
Whoo!
好了  我得走了  很高兴认识你
Well I've got to run. It was so nice to meet you
还有真的很开心和你重逢  小包
And so great to see you again Bobby.
哦  好的
Yeah. Okay.
凯蒂猫是吧
Kitty-kat huh?
好啦  我也可以给你取一个爱称的嘛
Well I could come up with a nickname for you.
比如说
Like...
其实这确实很有趣儿
You know it's really funny
因为我现在可是给你想出了一大堆绰号来了
'cause I'm thinking of a lot of nicknames for you.
好啊  亲亲男友
Hi boyfriend.
好啊  亲亲女友
Hi girlfriend.
嗨  埃米特
Hi Emmett.
某女友哈
Girlfriend.
你们俩在排练吗  我是不是最好等会儿再来
You guys are rehearsing. Should I come back later?
-不用啊  -当然了
- No. - Yes.
不用  我们就快弄完了
No we're just finishing up.
对吧
Aren't we?
我们五分钟前才刚开始的啊
We started five minutes ago.
那可是很有质量的五分钟
It was a good five minutes.
我觉得好像打扰到你们了
I feel like I'm intruding.
-不  你没有  -是的  你确实打扰了
- No you're not.  - Yes you are.
我去楼上好了
I'll be upstairs.
再来吧  一 二  一二三四
Okay one two one two three four...
不  埃米特  先停下
No Emmett stop.
咋了
What?
我不喜欢刚才你跟我女朋友讲话的态度
I don't like the way you were talking to my girlfriend.
我也不喜欢她来打扰我们的排练
I don't like the way she's interrupting our rehearsal.
她对我们计划一点都不尊重
She has no respect for the process.
我们根本没订过计划
We don't have a process.
她又不知道这一点
She doesn't know that.
所有人都知道的好吧
Everyone knows that.
到底哪一边对你更重要呢
What's more important to you...
你的马子还是这乐队
your girlfriend or this band?
弄这乐队我就是为了钓马子
This band was just a way to get girls
现在我目的达到了
Which I did.
好得很
Fine.
那么这个乐队的使命也完成了
Then this band is through.
我会带着我的鼓  从此离开你的生活
I'll take my drums and get out of your life.
有人会过来收拾我的物品的
Someone will be by to collect my things.
嘿  你在这外面做什么呢
Hey what are you doing out here?
我在想事情
Just thinking.
PJ和感应乐队今天解散了
P.J. and the Vibe broke up today.
哦  儿子你要知道能维持一个乐队的团结确实很难
Oh well son it's hard to keep a band together.
你们俩也确实经历过一些挑战的难关
And you guys did have some challenges
大多数是有关音乐的
Most of them musical.
要不是埃米特嫉妒我有女朋友
We'd still be together
那我们还可以继续在一起啊
if Emmett wasn't jealous of my girlfriend.
儿子啊  你和梅迪森腻在一起的时间多得吓死人
Son you've been spending an awful lot of time with Madison.
你有没有想过也许埃米特感觉被排斥了
Now did you ever consider that maybe Emmett feels rejected?
被我的女朋友吗
By my girlfriend?
是被你啊
By you.
就因为我有了女朋友
Because I have a girlfriend.
因为你忽视了他
Because you've been ignoring him.
因为我的女朋友呗
Because of my girlfriend.
PJ  我也快要跟你崩了
P.J. I'm ready to break up with you.
儿子  你不应该让姑娘
Son you can't let a girl
介入到你和你最好朋友的友谊之间
Come between you and your best friend.
但梅迪森比埃米特更温柔芬芳啊
But Madison's softer and smells better than Emmett.
听着  相信我  好吗
Look trust me on this okay?
以前我也几乎犯过同样的错误
I nearly made the same mistake
那时我在跟梅迪森她妈妈约会呢
When I was dating Madison's mom.
真的吗  发生过什么事
Really? What happened?
凯瑟琳太黏人了
Katherine was too clingy
有太多的需要
Too demanding.
她总是插在我和我的朋友们之间
She came between me and my friends
所以最终我做了该做的事情
So I did what I had to do...
放她离开
Let her go
说声再见
Said goodbye
再也不是她的亲亲小包了
No more Bobby love for her.
亲亲小包  她是这样叫的你啊
Bobby love? That's what she called you?
哦  你懂的
Oh you know it.
这段往事我们没必要告诉你妈
Um that one we don't need to share with your mom.
真是古怪  一般那些被我揍过的孩子家
This is weird. I don't usually get invited
不会邀请我过来玩的
To play dates with the kids I beat up.
关于那个嘛  我跟盖比聊过了
About that... I talked to Gabe
我发现他也算是喜欢你
And turns out he kinds of likes you too.
他真的吗
He does?
你为什么要捏紧拳头呢
Why are you clenching your fist?
我感觉到那种想揍人的兴奋
I feel like punching someone.
好了  我们先要来解决这个问题
Okay well we need to work on
要教你怎么向男孩们表达自己的感情
how you express yourself with boys.
不如我们来玩一下角色表演小游戏
Why don't we try a little role-playing okay?
我来当盖比  你就当你自己
I'll be Gabe.You'll be you.
好吧
Okay.
那我们就假装是在学校里碰到啦
So let's pretend we run into each other at school.
-嗨  阿乔  -嗨  盖比
- Hi Jo.  - Hi gabe.
你的外套很好看哟
I like your jacket.
看来某人的空手套功夫不错啊
Well somebody knows karate.
对不起  这是条件反射
Sorry. It was a reflex.
让我再来一次吧
Let me try again.
是可以  不过再来一次的时候
Okay but this time
我们都动口不动手  好不
Let's keep our hands to ourselves okay?
知道啦
Got it.
好的  嗨  阿乔
Okay. Hi Jo.
嗨  盖比
Hi Gabe.
午饭时要不要和我坐一起呢
Want to sit with me at lunch?
看招
Yah!
看来你钻了个语法漏洞
I see you found a loophole.
你又没说不能动脚
You didn't say anything about the feet.
而你现在也学会这个单词“漏洞”了
And now you've learned the word "loophole."
好再来试一次
Now try this time
不许动手也不许动脚
With no hands and no feet
任何你能用来打我的东西都不行
Or anything else you could hit me with.
知道啦
Got it.
嗨  阿乔  你看上去很漂亮
Hi Jo. You look nice.
很好  阿乔
Very good Jo.
你捏紧了拳头又松开了
You clenched your fist and then you unclenched.
这就是进步啊
That is called progress.
不打人总觉得怪怪的
Feels weird without hitting
但我也有点喜欢这样
But I kind of like it.
她在这里干什么
What is she doing here?
不要紧的啦  你不用担心
No no it's okay. You have nothing to worry about.
对吗  阿乔
Right Jo?
嗯  对
Right.
你好  盖比  你看上去蛮不错
Hey Gabe. You look nice.
啥
What?
她称赞你了  赶快也回她一些好话呀
She gave you a compliment. Say something nice back.
呃
Uh...
你的头发比你的拳头更柔软呀
Your hair looks softer than your fists?
谢谢
Thanks.
你们俩个小朋友不如一起玩一会儿吧
Why don't you two hang out for a while?
我会在楼上考虑一下
I'll be upstairs trying to decide
我到底是要用冰敷还是热敷
If I should apply ice or heat.
那你喜欢玩什么
So what do you like to do?
我喜欢玩怪物卡车
I like monster trucks
混合格斗术  还有洋娃娃
Mixed martial arts and dolls.
你喜欢玩电动游戏吗
You like video games?
你都有什么游戏啊
What do you got?
死亡银河系
"Galaxy of Death."
是不是暴力级别的
Is it violent?
打到二级就有呕吐袋道具了
Level two comes with the barf bags.
真是好玩极了
It's really fun.
你用呕吐袋这招套牢我了
You had me at barf bag.
咦  你来做什么
Hey what are you doing here?
我正在送外卖途中
I'm between deliveries
不过我真的想跟你说些事
But I really wanted to say something to you.
第一  我真的由衷地开心你是我的女朋友
First I'm like totally psyched that you're my girlfriend.
那很好啊  还有呢
Great. Anything else?
那个  我在想啊
Well yeah. I was just thinking
我们是不是可以减少一些相处的时间呢
That we should be spending a little less time together
这样我们可以留一些时间给各自的朋友
You know so we still have time for friends.
我同意
Works for me.
又不是要现在就开始  梅迪森  怎么回事啊
Not starting right now. Madison what's going on?
没什么
Nothing.
我得去工作了  宝贝
Gotta get to work babe.
那是谁
Who's that?
没人啊
Nobody.
下次见  宝贝
See you later babe.
帽子很赞
Nice hat.
多谢
Thanks.
你的也不赖
You too.
那人是谁啊
Who was that?
只是来送披萨外卖的
Just the pizza delivery guy.
是吗  他们不是应该
Really? Don't they usually deliver pizzas
把披萨送到你家  而不是从你家送出去啊
To your house not from your house?
我不是
I don't...
他们也不会去亲顾客
And don't they usually not kiss the customers
还管顾客叫做“宝贝”吧
And call them "babe"?
你瞒着我和海盗披萨店的人搞上了
You were cheating on me with Pizza Pirate.
错了  其实我是瞒着海盗披萨男
No actually I was cheating on Pizza Pirate
和咕唧炸鸡男搞上了
With kwikki chikki.
那够了  咱俩完了
That's it. We're through.
你是要和我分手吗
Are you breaking up with me?
除非你答应我再也不见那个人
Unless you promise never to see him again.
那我们还是分手好了
Yeah we should probably break up.
他送给我了一大堆的优惠券呢
He gave me a whole bunch of coupons.
放开我  救命啊  哎哟
Get off me! Help! Ow!
阿乔  你在干什么啊
Jo what are you doing?
这可不是表达情感的好办法
This is not the way to express yourself.
这和我喜欢盖比没什么关系
This is not about me liking Gabe.
这是因为他在死亡银河系游戏里作弊
This is about him cheating at "Galaxy of Death."
我没作弊啊
I didn't cheat.
快把这疯子从我身上弄走
Get this whacko off me!
够了  阿乔  快放开他
Come on Jo get off him.
松手  松手
Let go. Let go.
哇呀
Whoa!
你也想试试这滋味吗
You want some of this?
嘿  查莉啊
Hey Charlie.
今天真是邓肯家孩子们的倒霉日子
Well today was a bad day for the Duncan kids.
我们学到了  有时候爱会伤害别人
We learned that sometimes love hurts.
不是开玩笑的  阿乔弄伤了我的肩膀
No kidding. Jo dislocated my shoulder.
梅迪森伤了我的心
Madison dislocated my heart.
好吧  也许等我们再长大一些再去爱会更容易些
Well maybe love gets easier as we get older.
亲爱的  也许这个不像凯蒂猫  可至少也是个昵称啊
Honey it's no Kitty-kat but at least it's a nickname.
小胖艾米吗
Amy-potomus?
好了  其实你这样说感觉根本不对嘛
Well when you say it like that...
也许  爱从来就不简单
Or maybe love never gets easier.
看来你又一次将要成为我们之中能解决这问题的人了
Then again you might be the one to figure that out.
祝你好运了  查莉
Good luck with that Charlie.
嘿
Hi.
我听说你和女友分手了
Heard about your breakup.
谁告诉你的
Who told you?
我看到你更改了网上微博状态啊
I saw you change your online status
从“谈恋爱”变成“被甩了”
From "in a relationship" to "dumped."
到哥们儿这儿来抱抱吧
Bring it here.
我真的被伤得很深啊
It hurts so much.
我懂的  埃米特在这里呢
I know. Emmett's here.
都哭出来吧
Let it out.
还有别去听我最后的语音留言了
And ignore my last voicemail.
-什么  -没啥  没啥  没啥
- What? - No no no no.
嗨  盖比  书包不错
Hey Gabe. Nice backpack.
你又想干什么  阿乔
What do you want Jo?
我想我表示得很清楚了啊  我想要你的书包
I think I was pretty clear. I want your backpack.
不行
No.
不好意思  你刚才是说不了吗
I'm sorry did you just say no?
没错
You heard me.
你再也不能欺负我了
You're not bullying me anymore.
怎样啊  你还能再打发你的姐姐来对付我吗
What you're gonna sic your sister on me again?
我又不怕她
I'm not afraid of her.
我可不止只有一个姐妹啊
I have more than one sister.
来看看她刚上了一堂空手道课的成果吧
And that's after only one karate lesson.